{"sid": "NT4BQVGPYU07_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 330113, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 330114, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 339286]], "time_left_end": "291", "answered_time": 339286, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "291", "question_time_start": 339287, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 343938]], "time_left_end": "287", "answered_time": 343938, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "287", "question_time_start": 343938, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 351101]], "time_left_end": "280", "answered_time": 351101, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "280", "question_time_start": 351101, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 355297]], "time_left_end": "275", "answered_time": 355297, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "275", "question_time_start": 355297, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 360624]], "time_left_end": "270", "answered_time": 360624, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "270", "question_time_start": 360625, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 365212]], "time_left_end": "265", "answered_time": 365212, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "265", "question_time_start": 365212, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 367968]], "time_left_end": "263", "answered_time": 367968, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "263", "question_time_start": 367969, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 371892]], "time_left_end": "259", "answered_time": 371892, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "259", "question_time_start": 371893, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 385703]], "time_left_end": "245", "answered_time": 385703, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "245", "question_time_start": 385703, "question": "58+14", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["submit", 388680]], "time_left_end": "242", "answered_time": 388680, "user_answer": "72", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 388680, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "242", "question_time_start": 388680, "question": "3+96+39", "correct_answer": 138, "events": [["submit", 393484]], "time_left_end": "237", "answered_time": 393484, "user_answer": "138", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "237", "question_time_start": 393484, "question": "27+869", "correct_answer": 896, "events": [["submit", 401522]], "time_left_end": "229", "answered_time": 401522, "user_answer": "906", "user_correct": "False", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "229", "question_time_start": 401523, "question": "7+4+3+84", "correct_answer": 98, "events": [["submit", 408572]], "time_left_end": "222", "answered_time": 408572, "user_answer": "98", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "222", "question_time_start": 408572, "question": "9+74+96", "correct_answer": 179, "events": [["submit", 416070]], "time_left_end": "215", "answered_time": 416070, "user_answer": "179", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "215", "question_time_start": 416070, "question": "7+28+84", "correct_answer": 119, "events": [["submit", 423993]], "time_left_end": "207", "answered_time": 423993, "user_answer": "119", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "207", "question_time_start": 423993, "question": "13+629", "correct_answer": 642, "events": [["submit", 429432]], "time_left_end": "201", "answered_time": 429432, "user_answer": "642", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "201", "question_time_start": 429433, "question": "74+43+63+66", "correct_answer": 246, "events": [["submit", 445182]], "time_left_end": "185", "answered_time": 445182, "user_answer": "246", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "185", "question_time_start": 445182, "question": "46+19", "correct_answer": 65, "events": [["submit", 450188]], "time_left_end": "180", "answered_time": 450188, "user_answer": "65", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "180", "question_time_start": 450188, "question": "8+7+4+97", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 459772]], "time_left_end": "171", "answered_time": 459772, "user_answer": "118", "user_correct": "False", "score": "15"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "171", "question_time_start": 459773, "question": "34+47", "correct_answer": 81, "events": [["submit", 464000]], "time_left_end": "167", "answered_time": 464000, "user_answer": "81", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 464000, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "167", "question_time_start": 464000, "question": "3+6+6+63", "correct_answer": 78, "events": [["submit", 472702]], "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 472702, "user_answer": "78", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 472702, "question": "6+8+4+99", "correct_answer": 117, "events": [["submit", 481633]], "time_left_end": "149", "answered_time": 481632, "user_answer": "117", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "149", "question_time_start": 481633, "question": "9+68+58", "correct_answer": 135, "events": [["submit", 491748]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 491748, "user_answer": "135", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 491749, "question": "6+69+99", "correct_answer": 174, "events": [["submit", 497386]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 497386, "user_answer": "174", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 497387, "question": "33+468", "correct_answer": 501, "events": [["submit", 504032]], "time_left_end": "127", "answered_time": 504032, "user_answer": "491", "user_correct": "False", "score": "19"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "127", "question_time_start": 504032, "question": "33+84", "correct_answer": 117, "events": [["submit", 510897]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 510897, "user_answer": "117", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 510897, "question": "43+456", "correct_answer": 499, "events": [["submit", 517121]], "time_left_end": "113", "answered_time": 517121, "user_answer": "499", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "113", "question_time_start": 517121, "question": "19+99+97+26", "correct_answer": 241, "events": [["submit", 537500]], "time_left_end": "93", "answered_time": 537500, "user_answer": "251", "user_correct": "False", "score": "20"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "93", "question_time_start": 537500, "question": "3+98+69", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["submit", 544397]], "time_left_end": "86", "answered_time": 544397, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "86", "question_time_start": 544398, "question": "77+29", "correct_answer": 106, "events": [["submit", 551877]], "time_left_end": "79", "answered_time": 551877, "user_answer": "106", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 551877, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "79", "question_time_start": 551877, "question": "77+49+76+48", "correct_answer": 250, "events": [["calc_7", 563301], ["calc_6", 563826], ["calc_+", 564209], ["calc_7", 564701], ["calc_6", 565230], ["calc_=", 566093], ["submit", 579463]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "51", "answered_time": 579463, "user_answer": "250", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "51", "question_time_start": 579463, "question": "7+68+34", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 585779]], "time_left_end": "45", "answered_time": 585779, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "45", "question_time_start": 585779, "question": "98+157", "correct_answer": 255, "events": [["submit", 591314]], "time_left_end": "39", "answered_time": 591314, "user_answer": "255", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "39", "question_time_start": 591314, "question": "8+56+69", "correct_answer": 133, "events": [["submit", 602360]], "time_left_end": "28", "answered_time": 602360, "user_answer": "134", "user_correct": "False", "score": "24"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "28", "question_time_start": 602360, "question": "3+3+4+27", "correct_answer": 37, "events": [["submit", 610753]], "time_left_end": "20", "answered_time": 610753, "user_answer": "37", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "20", "question_time_start": 610753, "question": "8+83+89", "correct_answer": 180, "events": [["calc_8", 616189], ["calc_3", 616694], ["calc_+", 617113], ["calc_8", 617583], ["calc_9", 617901], ["calc_=", 618469], ["submit", 624311]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "6", "answered_time": 624311, "user_answer": "180", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "6", "question_time_start": 624311, "question": "7+7+4+56", "correct_answer": 74, "events": []}}}}}